https://portadam.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentRequest a Quote
Newsletter Sign-UpPortadam Temporary Cofferdams, Flood Protection and Water StorageInnovative water diversion solutions. Call Us 856-740-0606
Menu	HomeResources
About Us
Portadam OverviewSustainabilityEnvironmental ImpactHistoryVideosRecent ProjectsLibraryTestimonialsFlood Protection
Flood Protection OverviewPortfolio of Flood Fighting SolutionsFlood Protection Photos & VideosFlood Prevention Projects
Fitzgerald Casino Case StudyFlood Prevention Success StoriesRigorously Tested and Certified
US Army Corps of EngineersBritish Standards InstituteFlood Risk Analysis ReportFlood Protection ResourcesCofferdams
Cofferdam OverviewCofferdam ProjectsCase Studies
D&G Boring Case StudySkanska Case StudyWater Storage
Water Storage OverviewWater Storage ProjectsAdvantagesFree WebinarCONTACT US!
ContactJoin Our TeamQuote | Site Survey RequestRequest a FREE WebinarEmail Newsletter SignupLast updated: 10/10/17Portadam, Inc. ("us", "we", or "our") operates https://www.portadam.com (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.Information We CollectGenerally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to us when using our Website.As a Visitor, you can browse our website to find out more about our Website. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor.Computer Information CollectedWhen you use our Website, we automatically collect certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Website. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information. We also collect the following:CookiesOur Website uses "Cookies" to identify the areas of our Website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.Third Party Tracking ToolsWe also use third party tracking tools to improve the performance and features of our Website. These third party tracking tools are designed to collect only Non-Personal Information about your use of our Website. However, you understand that such tools are created and managed by parties outside our control. As such, we are not responsible for what information is actually captured by such third parties or how such third parties use and protect that information.We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise on third party sites to you after you visited our Site. We and our third party vendors, like Google, use first party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Site.You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page. Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.Automatic InformationWe automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the website from which you entered our Website, if any, as well as the name of the website to which you're headed when you leave our website. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Website provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Website. How We Use Your InformationWe use the information we receive from you as follows:Customizing Our WebsiteWe may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to customize our Website.Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third PartiesWe do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes.Data AggregationWe retain the right to collect and use any Non Personal Information collected from your use of our Website and aggregate such data for internal analytics that improve our Website and Service as well as for use or resale to others. At no time is your Personally Identifiable Information included in such data aggregations.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Changes To This Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy is effective as of 10/10/17 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
MENU HomeResourcesAbout UsPortadam OverviewSustainabilityEnvironmental ImpactHistoryVideosRecent ProjectsLibraryTestimonialsFlood ProtectionFlood Protection OverviewPortfolio of Flood Fighting SolutionsFlood Protection Photos & VideosFlood Prevention ProjectsFitzgerald Casino Case StudyFlood Prevention Success StoriesRigorously Tested and CertifiedUS Army Corps of EngineersBritish Standards InstituteFlood Risk Analysis ReportFlood Protection ResourcesCofferdamsCofferdam OverviewCofferdam ProjectsCase StudiesD&G Boring Case StudySkanska Case StudyWater StorageWater Storage OverviewWater Storage ProjectsAdvantagesFree WebinarCONTACT US!ContactJoin Our TeamQuote | Site Survey RequestRequest a FREE WebinarEmail Newsletter Signup
